TorrentCounter.to - Download HD & BluRay Movies in Small Size
Train No 0377 going from
Allahabad to Gomtinagar...
...the Vivah Special Express,
will soon leave from Platform No. 3.
This is a special train.
It is overbooked.
They say, matches are made in heaven,
but the timing is decided here,
on earth.
In the city of Allahabad alone, 13,000
weddings will take place... today.
One would think that the
entire Indian economy runs on
the business of conducting weddings.
And we, the loyal citizens,
are running,
to make our contributions
toward the economy.
I am Kartik Singh, and I'm running...
And I am Aman Tripathi,
and I'm running as well.
I was six,
the first time I had to run.
The local boys hated my hair colour.
The only thought I had,
every time I ran was...
One day, I could be like
the superstar Amitabh Bachchan.
'I have never followed anyone...
always taken the lead.'
Two whacks from my father,
taught me two things.
One: Running doesn't
help you grow up any faster.
Two: You can't just
become a superstar...
You have to be born as one.
In my case, I was running
away from love, not violence.
As my family was running after me,
to put cake on my face.
Mummy always said that I am different.
But all their love, coupled
with all that frosting on my face...
made me look no different from them.
I've been running ever since.
But today, it's a different story.
Does your toothpaste celebrate love?
Hey Kartik, nobody here is
interested in celebrating their love.
So what, if they are not listening?
We will make ourselves heard.
How do we do that?
Go and sit on that kiddie train.
Crazy or what?
Go on, I have to fight these germs.
Are you on a holiday or what?
Get up!
Hello?
Mummy?
Does your toothpaste celebrate love?
Don't know about my toothpaste.
But I do have a heart that
beats for my darling Guddu.
Wait a minute.
Hold on, Guddu.
Down with black cauliflowers!
These farmers protesting against the
black cauliflowers are driving us mad.
So, when are you coming home?
Goggle is getting married.
We'll leave early morning tomorrow.
Our train leaves at 06:55.
Get some more of these.
Mummy, I won't be going home.
I had told you.
How many times must I repeat myself?
You idiot!
Is this why I gave
you those polio drops?
So you could keep running
away from me, huh?
I'm very busy, Mummy.
I keep telling you this.
I don't need your money.
What does 10,000 amount to, anyway?
Fine, don't come.
There's a wedding taking place,
the entire family is coming together.
And you can't make it!
So what?
They are around anyway.
Step out of the door
and they're all there.
Die! You bloody dog!
May you lose your job!
I hope you break your hand!
Does your toothpaste celebrate love?
All you can think of is whether
your toothpaste can love you.
What about all the love
you've got from the family?
Hang up now.
Now that you've called
and I'm getting billed for it,
go on, carry on with your ranting.
We were never outgoing anyway,
we'll become incoming again.
Bye!
Does your toothpaste celebrate love?
Aunty, should I keep a
mosquito coil in Guddu's room?
Or is he still allergic to it?
Guddu is dead!
He got run over...
cut into two pieces.
The top half was claimed by his work.
And the bottom half...
Is this because of a girl?
Kusum!
The black cauliflower created by
agricultural scientist,
Shri Shankar Tripathi
has created unrest among
the farmers in UP.
Oh God!
Where is Guddu's father?
Mummy!
Aren't we supposed to
complete these rituals on time?
I've been ready and
waiting for so long...
and no one is bothered.
Everyone's busy catching
stupid cauliflowers.
Wait, my turn.
Move. Move away.
May God help you.
You can't even handle a cauliflower,
how will you handle your wife?
I'll be able to handle everything,
just get married, Uncle.
How will he get you married?
Uncle, move, a black cauliflower!
He hasn't been able to get his
daughter married in all these years!
She is getting married tomorrow.
I couldn't find a suitable boy.
It did take some time,
but I've finally found somebody.
You haven't.
It's your brother who
has found... that ancient relic.
Any longer, and he would
have become a museum exhibit.
Mummy!
Don't you dare badmouth Ashok.
I'll set the house on fire,
let me tell you.
Where is he?
Should we start the rituals?
Has anyone seen Guddu's father?
Oh God, these damn cauliflowers.
Chaman!
Yes, what happened?
Have you seen Guddu's father?
He's there, on the terrace.
This damn terrace
is like his mistress...
he's always on top of it.
Let's go.
Down with the black cauliflower!
The cauliflower has ruined us all.
Shankar Tripathi, shame on you!
There is always hope...
Have you seen this, Uncle?
A miracle.
Let me gift you a sack
of these black cauliflowers.
No, no thank you, Shankar.
Take it. It's good for the children,
very nutritious.
This is what we've been
eating for the past week.
- Really?
- Yes!
Did you hear that, Gauri Shankar?
He's been eating this since
the past week, and he's still alive.
He's fine.
Tell me something, these
farmers who say they've been ruined...
were they any better off, earlier?
Er...
No way!
Their cauliflowers get infested with
worms,
- See this, Uncle.
- our black cauliflowers don't.
What's this?
Our neighbourhood.
Wow!
Gauri Shankar, our neighbourhood
is featured on the internet.
This is...
our house. And isn't this...
Mr. Mishra's terrace?
Correct, those are his wife's
undergarments put up for drying. See.
It's theirs.
Whatever.
It's great that our neighbourhood
is featured on the internet.
I'll celebrate by giving all of
you a sack of black cauliflowers each.
Where are you?
I'm right here. What happened?
See this, Uncle.
Why are you creating a ruckus?
I'm right here.
Kusum.
She's Mr. Nagar's daughter, isn't it?
I've spoken to her mother
and booked her for the past one year.
Booked her for what?
For our Guddu.
Right.
What do you mean right?
I've been stalling for a year now.
Gifting dry fruits won't work anymore.
I'd thought of getting Guddu married to
her when he'd visit for Goggle's wedding.
But your darling son
has refused to come home.
Where are you running off to?
I'm feeling shy, Aunty.
Let's finalise things first.
Okay, you can go.
Take this... bangle.
It's a gift from me
and a promise from his side.
But...
God bless you...
You better practice calling me Mummy,
from now.
Go on.
Don't misplace it.
I have just the one - bangle and son.
Why don't you say something?
What can I say, madam Sunaina?
You're the one speaking on my behalf.
Don't worry, I'll speak to Guddu.
He'll come home.
Brother!
Hurry up! The police are
about beat up the protestors.
No... it's okay.
Will someone start with the rituals?
Mummy, I guess we're done.
I'm ready to get married now.
Keshav, start the music.
Our lives have come together as one
Just like the river meets the sea
I want our lives
to flow together forever
Knowing you I have realised
That life can be so beautiful
I always want to be with you
Whether we win over this world or not
Happiness will drive away our sorrows
When you are with me
Nothing else matters
You are all that I need
- This is Devika's house.
We'll help her elope.
Stop... stop.
Help me with the stand first.
Go in, what are you waiting for?
I will.
Keep the engine running.
I can't start this piece of junk.
Start it for me.
I've told you so many
times to get it repaired.
It will cost you 100 bucks.
But you're so stingy.
You scared?
Shit scared.
Come here.
We'll handle everything.
Devika!
You dog!
I've been waiting for so long.
It's my first time...
getting a girl to elope.
Really?
As if I elope every single day.
What if we get caught?
Let me jump first.
I'll keep an eye on your father.
Okay.
If he comes out,
I'll make a run for it.
What about me?
I'll keep hanging from the balcony?
Tell him that you were
drying clothes and you fell.
You dumbass, my father
watches quiz shows all the time.
He's not stupid.
By the way, we have a dryer at home.
We don't put clothes
out to dry on the balcony.
'That's the right answer.'
If your father had brains, he would've
put a grill around the balcony.
What do you mean?
Girls who have open balconies
are the first ones to have affairs.
All the Delhi boys know this.
Girls living on first
floors are easy targets.
Have you come to help me elope
or to explain first floor-second floor
dynamics, in this ridiculous costume?
Kartik!
What's taking you so long?
This piece of junk has stopped again.
What?
Oh God!
Listen, the commercial
break will get over in a minute.
Dad won't budge from
his seat after that.
Next up is the
million-dollar question...
Followed by a three-minute
lecture by the host.
Yes, that much he deserves.
Then again,
there will be a commercial break.
You have five minutes
to get me out of here.
Okay?
Will your boyfriend, Ravi turn up?
There is no guarantee
for first loves.
Ravi isn't my first love,
and you know that.
He has sent me the location pin and...
100,000 bucks in cash.
OMFG!
So much cash!
It's from the Education Policy
that Dad had bought for me.
Kartik!
Policies mature way
before daughters do, here.
Hurry up.
Please take care of this,
Amitabh Bachchan.
Kartik! Hurry up, guys!
- 'One million!'
- Who is there?
Let's go, Aman!
- Start the bike!
- I can't!
- Kartik!
- Oh hell!
You guys can't get anything right!
Dad will kill me!
Start the bike!
Aman, come here!
Get him off me!
Grab him from the back.
Not me, grab him!
Run, Aman!
Stop!
Where are you going?
Why isn't he answering?
Aman, why weren't
you picking up the call?
'Coz he's busy picking up girls.
What're you saying, Uncle?
Give the phone to me.
Hello? Who is this? Hello?
You goon, how dare you touch him!
It's my father...
Don't you dare do anything to him.
Give my phone back.
Have you spoken to Guddu?
You were right.
This whole thing is about a girl.
I knew it.
He's a young man.
I'd asked you to keep an eye on him.
But you were so busy
with your black cauliflowers.
We've lost control of our son.
Guess I've lost my
gold bangle as well.
It's all because
of the farmers' curse.
Can you be quiet?
Let me think.
Your naïve son has got
entangled with a Delhi girl.
Do something about it.
What do I do?
Reel him in.
Catch those pests!
What the hell are you doing?
Those bloody losers ran away.
They got scared.
This is our area!
All I had to do was make a call.
Listen, let's go to your place.
We live together, remember?
I meant, your house in Allahabad.
Isn't your cousin getting married?
We won't go there.
I have the best plan.
We'll have a blast there.
What's wrong with you?
I'm not taking you there.
Why?
I'm worth it and you know it.
Nobody knows about
us back home, Kartik.
As if we'll tell them.
No wonder you're so scared.
We could go tell your father,
'Uncle, get us married as well.'
Very funny, huh?
We were helping Devika run away,
remember?
Now we're running away, ourselves.
I know, I've been
beaten black and blue.
All over.
But I don't care.
Anything for love.
It is the result
of someone else's love.
Love is love, after all.
Remember, we're the good germs.
They're the bad ones.
- We're the bad ones.
- Good germs.
- Bad.
- Good.
- I'm not going to Allahabad.
- Kartik, try to understand.
- Good.
- My family won't...
- We are good germs!
Stop shouting, they'll...
Where do we go now?
You loser, come here!
I'll teach you a lesson!
- Where are you going?
- Come on!
Rickshaw!
- Stop, stop!
- Come on!
Hurry up!
Get in!
Take us to Nizamuddin railway station.
Passengers, please pay attention.
Train No 0377 going from
Allahabad to Gomtinagar...
...the Vivah Special Express,
will soon leave from Platform No. 3.
Do you know the superhero Shaktiman?
Where are we?
Allahabad.
We've reached your hometown.
Get up.
What time does the train leave?
6:55 am.
Hurry up then.
Listen, if you meet Shaktiman,
tell him...
I know that Gangadhar
is the real Shaktiman.
Passengers, please pay attention...
...has arrived.
Oo la a... la la... ooo...
When the DJ plays a romantic song
My Baby follows me everywhere
She asks me to dance with her
And pulls me to the dance floor
When you come to me and I come to you...
Everybody sings Oo la a...
la la... ooo
Oo la a... la la... ooo...
Oh Sheila,
my shirt seems to be coming off
I am ready for some fun
I wonder why
Where have you come from?
You've set my heart on fire
Your moves drive me crazy
When I say, I love you
And you say, love you too
Everybody sings oo la la...
la la... ooo
Oo la la... la la... ooo...
What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
It's been so long.
I need your touch.
Everybody sings oo la la...
la la... ooo
Oo la la... la la... ooo...
He's an educated man.
I'm sure he knows.
No, seeing us glued together,
he'd think it's an ad for a glue!
He shouldn't come. I told him.
You're correct!
If nothing else works,
a glue will surely bring you together.
Let's put up a big sign at
the ITO crossing, of us kissing.
Kartik!
Dad has passed out and you're
still in the mood to fool around?
Why didn't you notice him there?
You didn't, either.
He's your father!
Stop shouting.
Will be delayed for sometime...
You know I am passionate
about everything, right?
I close my eyes every time I kiss you.
I don't care about anything around me.
I didn't see your father.
I close my eyes as
well when I kiss you.
I have passion in me as well.
When we get physical,
you complain that I'm distracted.
That I'm lost.
Today, I was completely focused.
Aww,
you're my strong baby.
My baby strongest!
You're wrong,
the phrase is, 'My Daddy Strongest'.
And this...
Kusum is looking at us.
I'm sure he has told them.
Everyone must be talking about it now.
Open your mouth.
Show me your teeth.
Why?
Because our teeth are
our strongest weapons.
Weapons of mass destruction.
Are we dogs?
We will be, if required.
A mother's motherly love...
A father's fatherly love...
An uncle's uncle-ly love.
And an aunt's...
What kind of love would she have?
I'm sure it's motherly
love as well, Kartik.
Whatever.
If they can use that as a weapon,
why can't we,
use our teeth as weapons?
You will be a dog. We will be dogs.
The first time my father
caught me with a boy...
...he beat the crap
out of me and... I bit him.
- Yeah, I became...
- A dog?
Yes.
I can't be one, Kartik.
He's my father.
What did he eat this morning?
Black cauliflower.
And last night?
What else would he eat?
He's a scientist.
It's his new creation.
The farmers have thrown tons
of this cauliflower at our doorstep.
It will feed four generations.
What's so funny?
I was just...
Wait, I've been slaving
in the kitchen all my life.
This has never happened.
It's the first time a random doctor
is questioning my cooking skills.
But...
Why don't you say something?
From now on,
all of you will cook your own food.
Come on Bhabhi, no one's blaming you.
Doctor, all the women
work together in the kitchen.
So, they are all to blame.
It's not our fault, Doctor.
It's the black cauliflower.
That's all we've been
eating for the last two weeks.
It's your daughter
who's getting married.
You don't need to act so coy, Champa.
I didn't say anything wrong.
I've ended up sleeping with black
cauliflowers, instead of Chaman.
This is how bad it is.
Look, this is your personal matter...
Wait a minute.
If you're so troubled,
find yourselves another house.
I've spent all my
life looking after you.
You? You've looked after us?
I wake up at 4 a.m. everyday!
I've been fetching buckets of water and
filling the water tank for 35 years now.
Cooking doesn't count for everything.
We'll fit a pipe to
the tank after you leave.
You need not worry about that.
So, that's how insignificant we are!
If he'd allowed to
Chaman to study law...
...we'd have had more
standing in this family.
Remember, it was Chaman
who couldn't clear the law exam.
We didn't stop anyone from studying.
And why did he fail the exam?
Why?
Questions were out of syllabus...
If their mother had given
Chaman almonds, as well...
...then he would have
definitely cleared the exam.
Why do all arguments
revolve around my law degree?
Champa's dream of being the queen of
the house has made her a drama queen.
We should have seen this coming...
...when we'd seen her family members
secretly eating omelettes, at her wedding.
Do you know Doctor, while
they claim they're pure vegetarians,
They're actually...
Why bring this up again?
Aunty...
It was an eggless omelette!
I've been hearing
this for 35 years now.
Everybody's out to spoil my big day.
They're jealous.
Goggle...
Move.
Bhabhi, you're the older one,
she's younger to you.
- Please...
- Shut up.
She has you dancing to her tunes.
You're totally henpecked.
Homeopathic or allopathic?
- Homeopathic.
- Allopathic.
Fine, I'll prescribe
some allopathic medicines.
Everyone is entitled
to his or her beliefs.
Get these medicines from the store.
Right now?
Of course.
Don't worry.
The train stops for
about 20 minutes here.
There is a protest up ahead.
Till then you can eat
your 'eggless' omelettes.
Get these, quickly.
- He is awake.
- Brother?
Don't worry, it's not a protest
against the black cauliflowers.
Many an ill befall us, Mr. Tripathi.
Now that you're up,
why don't you take a short walk?
Okay?
I'll take your leave now.
Let's go.
Move, Kusum.
This way, Doctor.
Why is he so quiet, Doctor?
I can only prescribe medicines for
what ails his body not what ails his mind.
Nice.
You write poetry as well?
No.
People pay to hear my diagnosis.
Who would pay, to hear poetry?
But it was good.
Snacks! Snacks!
Oh, he's here.
- Go. Go and speak to him.
- I won't.
Come on.
Go and tell him that you love
me and nothing can keep us apart.
How do I go and talk to him?
He looks like he'll throw up,
every time he sees me.
I won't go. I'm scared.
This is the time. Be an angry
young man, like Vijay in Deewar.
Be a man. Be like Vijay,
the one who stays undefeated.
Really?
He looked quite defeated to me,
in Deewar...
..when Ravi threw the
'Mother' punch line at him.
What the hell!
The parents of the world seem to have
the best punch lines in all arguments.
Let's go together.
If Vijay and Ravi approach
them together, things will get sorted.
Yeah, right.
And I'll be the one
getting beaten up twice.
First by my own father
and then by yours.
I'm not going with you, you coward!
I'm going back to Delhi.
Hello, train? Train! Hello!
Okay fine. I'm going, Kartik.
Listen,
my father is an uneducated blacksmith.
He doesn't get all this.
But your father is
an educated man... he will.
Try and be a hero, bro.
Hell, why did I call you bro?
What do I say?
The truth.
Why do I fall for this emotional...
I love Kartik, Papa.
We can't live without each other.
I love you, Papa. I mean Kartik.
I love you too, Papa.
I love Kartik, Papa.
- Come on, get on top and fix it.
- Wait!
Everyone will get water.
This is not right.
What, sir?
This is not the right way.
Hold the pipe like this.
Papa?
Turn it on.
Yes.
What did I tell you?
There's a science to this.
Papa?
What are you doing?
It hurts!
Papa!
It's very hot...
prickly heat, you know.
This is the best way to beat the heat.
It's okay.
You can always change.
Chaman's clothes will fit you.
Listen, stay away from that boy.
This is not right.
Your sister is getting married,
come on.
Get up.
What's wrong?
Papa is looking at us.
What are you doing here?
What did I do?
I didn't do anything.
What can I do?
Shankar Tripathi,
son of Deenanath Tripathi, is useless.
A father, who can't control his son,
is useless.
Did you speak to Guddu?
Did he tell you about the girl?
This boy, I tell you,
will embarrass us with this girl.
That embarrassment
would be nothing, but he...
What kind of embarrassment?
What are you talking about?
Aunty!
What?
Sorry, Mummy.
So, which one do you like?
This one? Or that one?
The yellow one.
What about him?
Who?
- Him.
- Who 'him'?
Aman.
She's right here!
She's here! Kusum is here!
Someone's calling you.
Yes, I heard.
You should go immediately
when someone calls you.
Else, it's bad luck.
Now that you'll be
our daughter-in-law...
Sunaina...
I hope this girl is patient.
Else, all our hopes will get dashed.
What are you talking about?
I don't get it.
Are you feeling okay?
Sunaina...
I'm very upset today.
Okay, I'll give in this one time.
It's not often that you're so upset.
It took me a long
time to wear this sari.
You'll have to help me wear it again.
Let's go.
Goggle! What is this, my dear?
You asked for a band, I arranged it.
You asked for a wedding procession,
I arranged it.
Now what's this tantrum
about going on a horse?
Don't label my desires
as tantrums, Papa!
It might be Ashok's second one, but
it's the first time I'm getting married.
If he doesn't want to come on a horse,
fine. I will.
What will his family think?
Why bother worrying about it?
Let's go and find out.
Go. Fly on an aeroplane
for all I care!
Where's Mummy?
Will anybody help me here?
You can dance later.
Let's move it.
Where were you?
What?
There's a special
arrangement in that car.
What arrangement? Take me there.
What?
Take me to that car.
Take me there!
Have you forgotten who
gave you your first drink?
Brother?
Get me a cigarette.
What did you say?
Give me a fag.
Hey, give me a cigarette.
I don't smoke, Uncle.
Here, take this.
Hope he didn't get hit on the head
by one of those black cauliflowers.
Get lost.
What's wrong with you people?
I'm waiting to go and get married...
and everyone's busy showing
off their dance moves.
To hell with all of you.
Lead this horse, brother.
I don't need them.
I'll get married by myself.
Lead the horse from that
side and go straight to the altar.
Move aside.
You are our daughter-in-law!
Won't you seek our blessings first?
Let me get married first, Uncle.
Then I'll seek blessings
from all of you.
Let's go.
Ashok's already there, right?
Yes, he's inside.
Come inside, everyone.
Goggle has already gone in.
Welcome. Hello.
He is my...
What happened?
You go. Go back to Delhi.
Are you goin' crazy?
I'm having such a blast.
Your family is so cool.
They are not cool at all.
Papa has been staring
at us the entire evening.
What has he done? To be your father.
Just given a single sperm!
Yes.
And I have to pay for that
single sperm all my life, Kartik.
You should leave.
You should take the next train.
Don't be crazy.
You are not to blame
for his behaviour.
I'll leave at dawn,
before anyone wakes up.
The way he's looking at us,
I don't know when we'll
see each other next.
Dance the night away with me.
Take your hands off, Kartik.
I'm not in the mood for dancing.
I'll get you in the mood.
Like always.
Come on, let's go.
I'll see you inside.
You'll have to handle it,
if things go wrong.
Bro!
Play something cool for my entry.
It should be sexy AF.
Putting up with your tantrums
And whims day and night
I roam around
With a broken heart
This dude is in love with you
Stop me if you can
This dude is scared of none
This dude is in love with you
Our bond cannot be broken
I'll give up the world
but won't give you up
Our bond cannot be broken
I'll give up the world
but won't give you up
This dude gives you his word
This dude is in love with you
I can let go of this world
But this dude won't let go of you
This dude is in love with you
Yes, this dude is crazy about you
What the f*&^!
Mummy...
Chaman!
Yes?
Do something, Chaman.
What can I do?
Why do I have to deal with 'out
of syllabus' questions, every time?
[CHANTS MANTRAS]
Everyone, please bow down
with folded hands.
We have been blessed.
A miracle.
It's our family tradition.
When... a girl gets married,
her elder brother...
and his best friend...
welcome... everyone like this.
Right.
Like this?
Yes.
But they are...
Kissing? Yes.
Not all kisses are romantic, you know.
Some kisses are formal ones.
But this one's on the lips.
Doesn't look formal to me.
You are not aware of our customs.
They're actually
exchanging cardamom seeds.
Right.
With their mouth?
Yes.
It's very auspicious.
It blesses the newly married couple.
That's enough.
Are you done exchanging?
Done!
They're done!
Congratulations!
Come, let's start
with the wedding rituals.
Let's start.
Come here, son.
- Please join us.
- Let's go.
That's enough.
You've done exactly as I had expected.
Enough.
Chaman!
Yes, Brother?
Chaman, take this boy away.
Put him into a train and
make sure he doesn't come back.
But, I have to give away my daughter,
according to the rituals.
I've been waiting for all these years.
I'll give her away. It's no big deal.
Come on, I'll see you off.
Let me just talk to Aman, okay?
No way!
Let me just speak to him, Uncle! Bro!
- Let me speak to him once.
- No way!
- I'll just say bye from afar.
Can I say a final goodbye, please?
Move aside.
You'll have to fight me for this.
I don't want to fight with you.
You may not know this,
we fight many battles
every day in our lives.
But the battles we
fight against our family,
are the toughest and
the most dangerous ones.
Take Arjun, for instance.
Mr. Mathur's son?
Is he also in your gang?
Come on, he's talking
about Arjun from Mahabharata.
You're going on a tangent here.
My daughter's getting married now.
General knowledge questions
are the last thing on my mind.
Why don't you record your speech
on a voice message and send it to us?
We'll get the entire family
to sit and listen to it.
Please, let's just go now.
Okay, let's go.
Pay up.
For what?
No matter what the world labels us.
We still have to
pay for a train ticket.
Here.
Hunger... will also strike me.
Obviously.
Here.
Covers the GST as well.
By the way Uncle Bro, be nice to him.
He's your son. He's just like you.
A hard nut.
Hey!
Chaman, get him out of here!
Get this disaster away from here!
Stay there till the
train leaves the platform.
Okay!
What... what are you doing?
Royal salutes... for
my father's bravery.
What do you mean?
Goggle?
- Sunaina, Goggle...
- Stop her!
They stopped the wedding midway!
Stop right there.
This wedding cannot take place.
What is the problem, Sushil?
If the elders are okay with it,
where's the problem?
Ashok is the eldest
member of our family.
And he has decided not to marry her.
That's it. Please leave.
But why?
Your boy likes boys.
Uncle, your son is gay.
Dad has refused to
go ahead with the wedding.
We don't want a stepmother.
You may leave now.
It's a mistake.
It's not like that. Brother!
Aman!
Tell me something, son...
When did you decide,
you'll be like this?
What?
I mean... this.
It's called being gay.
Same thing.
When did you decide it?
When did you decide, you won't be gay?
What's there to decide?
I'm born this way.
Really?
You have a valid point.
Do your parents know?
Stop.
Go on.
I'll take your leave, Uncle.
We'll meet again, if destined.
Remember one thing...
if you hurt Aman,
I'll find your address
and hunt you down.
Tell Shankar Tripathi,
if he wants to play god
...I can exert my powers as well.
Hello Champa, all well?
Are the wedding rituals over?
No...
Why are you crying?
Have you sent her off already?
Our...
I can't understand.
You are crying so much.
Give the phone to someone else.
- Uncle?
- Yes, Keshav?
Goggle took off.
But why?
Why did she take off with Ashok?
I was getting them married.
Not with Ashok,
she took off with the horse.
The horse?
Ashok's family called off the wedding,
that's why.
Called it off?
I'll slap you for this nonsense.
I'm reaching in two minutes.
She took off?
When the hell will this train arrive?
The train will be here soon.
Recite the poem, son.
Jack and Jill went up the hill
To fetch a pail of water.
Jack fell down and broke his crown,
Jill came tumbling after.
- Very good.
- It's wrong.
This poem is wrong.
Jack and Johnny went up the hill,
To live in love and laughter.
Jack got thrashed by his dad,
And Johnny hid soon after.
This is the right one.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you teaching him this rubbish?
What's wrong in this, Uncle?
Why does it have to be Jill,
who Jack always climbs the hill with?
Why can't Jack go with Johnny?
How do I know?
This is what is written in the books.
Has anyone ever asked
Jack whom he wants to go with?
Jill or Johnny?
That's why I am saying:
Jack and Johnny went up the hill,
To live in love and laughter.
Jack got thrashed by his dad,
And Johnny hid soon after.
Jack and Johnny went up the hill,
To live in love and laughter.
Jack got thrashed by his dad,
And Johnny hid soon after.
Jack and Johnny went up the hill,
To live in love and laughter.
Jack got thrashed by his dad,
And Johnny hid soon after.
Jack and Johnny went up the hill,
To live in love and laughter.
Jack got thrashed by his dad,
And Johnny hid soon...
Brother?
Goggle has run away.
We'll see.
What do you mean, 'we'll see'?
We can't find her.
Should we deal with
someone we can't find,
or do we deal with what
we have just found out?
Really!
Let's go, your highness!
Wait a minute, Brother.
She is my daughter.
Here, I'm trying to save
our family from embarrassment...
...and you're going on
and on about your daughter.
She's the one who decided
to run away, isn't it?
She'll return when she decides to.
All daughters belong
to someone else, anyway.
Put some sense into his head.
Let's go.
So when will that 'someone'
come and take her away?
What is this, Bhabhi?
- Why the sudden change?
- Bhabhi.
What if that 'someone' is no one?
You can't stop everyone.
People will talk.
We can't stop them.
Your misdeeds have
ruined Goggle's life.
It will ruin our family next.
Isn't it?
Why will this ruin our family?
I don't understand.
We are such a big family.
Who cares,
whose son is sleeping with whom?
What do you mean 'sleeping with'?
You'd said that you're
merely in love with him.
So, I'm allowed to love
him but not sleep with him?
Why are you going off on a tangent?
They must be roommates.
You are roommates, right?
I used to sleep with
Chaman when we were younger.
Sometimes in his sleep, he'd put
his legs on me, that doesn't mean...
In your sleep,
if you accidentally touch someone...
...it's not that
...what you think it is.
You are mistaken.
Nothing happened.
You are fine.
He's fine!
Yes, he is fine.
Come on, Papa, I'm not mistaken.
It's as if you want to pee
and I tell you that you're mistaken.
Is that even possible?
There's a difference between
peeing and loving, isn't there?
The body has physical needs.
What?
Have you ever been in love?
So what's left?
Peeing.
There is a science
behind wanting to pee.
Proper science.
Yes Papa, there is a
science behind loving as well.
Proper science.
Love is not a readymade
drink that you can just gulp down.
Mummy, the first time I saw Kartik,
it grew big.
Huh?
My eyes. My eyes grew big!
This happens when you're in love.
There's a science behind this.
At his mere touch, there was
an explosion of dopamine in my body.
Dopamine?
- It's a kind of...
- It's something our body secretes.
When you're in love,
it's released by the body.
I feel so stressed
when I'm away from him.
It happens because of corticotrophin.
Ohh!
Who are you reminded of?
Why are you sighing?
Kumar.
I'd tried telling you about him before
we got married, but you wouldn't listen.
Why are you getting angry at Mummy?
Just because you couldn't
be with the one you loved...
...doesn't mean you will
hate people who fall in love.
Have you forgotten
about your Yezdi bike?
You were about to elope...
against everybody's wishes with...
What was her name?
Rani Asthana.
I wanted to. But I didn't elope.
I married someone my
family wanted me to marry.
They succeeded in
stopping the wedding,
but, were they able to
stop you from being in love?
Papa, the first time I kissed Kartik,
in a cab...
...there was a burst
of cortisol in my body.
You must have experienced the same
when you kissed the one you loved,
for the first time.
What about you, Mummy?
Shut up.
Why do you want him to shut up?
Let him talk.
Yes, I was in love once.
But with a girl.
A woman.
You are in love with a boy.
A man!
What f&*king difference does it make?
What?
Did you just swear?
I am his father and...
I am. Right?
Of course, you are.
I'd just held hands with him.
I had stopped swearing so
that you wouldn't learn those words.
And this is how you talk to me?
It's not me,
it's the oxytocin talking.
It is manufactured in the
hypothalamus when you are in love.
It gives you goose bumps
and fires you from within.
Your behaviour changes and
you don't give a damn about anyone,
even if it's your father
standing in front of you.
How do I make my
hypothalamus understand?
That Kartik is a boy and so am I.
And that this should not
make a difference to anyone else.
- But son...
- Papa.
Aman...
We will get you treated.
There is nothing medical
science can't do nowadays.
Right?
You'll be fine.
Sure, Mummy.
Your oxytocin signals love
and mine signals a disease?
Aman!
Sunaina, take off your sari.
You're upset, again?
I can't do this again.
Sunaina, listen to me.
Take off your sari.
Somebody should think about
people who want to commit suicide.
Have a heart, you rascals!
What are you doing, Goggle?
Have you gone mad?
I want to kill myself.
But why?
My wedding was called off.
All because of you.
So you want to kill yourself
just because of that?
It's important to marry
to have a fulfilled life.
But one can die alone, right?
Enough now.
This is crazy.
All you've been talking
about is marriage!
- Did you ask me before...
-Shut up.
Be quiet.
No one will talk about marriage here.
It's as if marriage is
like a course of antibiotics...
something you must complete.
So what, if the wedding is called off?
Why do you want to die?
I was 15 when my boyfriend
tried to kiss me.
Seeing my fake eye freaked him out.
I've been waiting ever since.
Show it to me again!
Whoa, Conjuring!
He must've been shit scared.
We were on the terrace
and I pushed him off.
Now he is missing a
leg and I am missing an eye.
I felt guilty about it and
had to treat him like a brother.
Aman's father kept behaving like this
and now, you're behaving like this.
The entire family is bonkers.
Yes, we are.
Aman, your father is
trying to hang himself!
What are you up to?
Give me a minute.
Aman!
What happened?
It's our personal matter.
He is trying to commit suicide.
We'll solve this in five minutes.
Hurry up, Aman!
Move. Move.
Shit!
What are you doing?
You don't even know
how to commit suicide.
Aman will be right here.
Why are you in such a hurry?
You could have done this at home.
It's a personal matter.
It will be over in two minutes.
Wait, Goggle.
Where are you going?
To lie on the train tracks.
Don't!
Don't do that.
Why are you doing this?
You have your family to support you.
All I had was... a shadow of a father.
When I met all of
you for the first time,
I realised that I wanted
to be a part of this family.
This is the family
I want to get married into.
If you love him so much, why are you
running away and leaving him all alone?
I don't have anyone to love.
But you do.
You'll never be happy,
if you run away now.
Nor would Aman.
You knew about it?
Yeah, since childhood.
He had such big dreams for you.
He has done so much for you.
And this is how you repay it?
What are you punishing us for?
We've never asked anything from you?
Have we?
If you don't want to live here, fine.
We'll buy you a place in Delhi.
You don't need to
send any money back home.
But please listen to your father.
We have chosen Kusum as your bride.
She is a good girl.
She's a girl.
Agree to marry her.
Goggle, let's go.
Where?
To your place.
To my future in-laws.
I'm coming, Aman,
to set off some fireworks
in the Tripathi family.
We deserve
a happy ending as well.
After all that dance and
drama my knees are acting up.
Your knees are just as useless
as your black cauliflowers.
Should we have let him have his way?
Aman's our son, after all.
He's yours.
Our own.
Just like Goggle was.
Champa! Champa!
I meant... she is, will always be.
I'm sure Goggle is here, somewhere.
Be patient, Chaman.
Everything will be fine.
Chaman, what I meant is,
Aman's problem is affecting us all.
And together we'll have
to find a miracle cure.
Uncle!
I found something on Google.
It clearly states that being
gay is not a kind of disease.
See this.
Whose side are you on?
This Google's or ours?
The Tripathis have been
here way before 3G and 4G arrived.
Go and sit in the bus.
Chaman...
You have no sense of timing.
But...
'The issue of black cauliflowers has
taken a political turn in Allahabad.'
'It is said, because of this problem
the farmers are turning to violence.'
'It has resulted in
a curfew in Allahabad.'
Nobody from the Tripathi clan
has brought disgrace to the family.
And look at you, you've brought
the entire city to its knees.
Are you crazy?
Don't worry.
I'll fix your problem.
Fix me?
I am not some machine
that needs fixing.
I know what to do.
One minute.
Don't come so close.
Go and sit over there.
Okay?
With your chutzpah and my belief,
I'm sure we'll hit it off.
What?
Hit what?
Will you hit the ball out of the park,
after marriage?
Will there be billboards on us?
At the most, you'll have
more kids than the usual two.
Those kids will grow up thinking
they can hit it off, as well.
But in this country, kids get
hit way before they can hit it off.
You still have time.
Refuse to get married to me.
Else, it won't be a hit,
it'll be a miss.
I won't refuse to the marriage.
You're only concerned
with your own problem.
Listen, I maybe gay,
but this is not a problem for me.
Maybe not for you,
but it is a problem for your parents.
As soon as we get home,
I'll call Panditji
and get a pooja to mark
Aman's rebirth as a man.
It will solve everything.
It will be the first of its kind,
in Allahabad.
Okay?
That's a great idea.
Isn't it?
Let me tell Chaman about this.
Chaman!
Aunty!
He has gone to pee.
See, you are my last hope.
Please, don't refuse to marry me.
It's my request, please.
Aman!
It's a long journey.
Why don't you go ahead
and do it on all our behalf?
What you are doing is wrong.
Really?
Now I'll have to learn how to pee,
from you?
Who am I to teach you anything?
I am younger to you.
The elders have mastered the art of
peeing all over our hopes and desires.
Come on, which hope
of yours have I dampened?
Sort out your own issues.
You sort out your issues first.
Your daughter has run away from home.
It's all because of your son.
He is the reason she has done this.
No, no.
That's not the real reason.
The real reason is that you
were unable to find a groom for her.
You seem to have forgotten that she
lost her eye because of your airgun.
Because she lost an eye,
nobody wants to marry her.
Great.
And this is how you took your revenge?
You think I ruined
your daughter's life,
so you ruined my son's?
Isn't it?
All those CDs with dirty
movies that you'd keep in your room,
Aman would secretly watch them all.
There were girls,
featured in those movies.
But your son is interested in boys.
Only girls, huh?
We need evidence here.
Mr. Lawyer, why are you silent now?
Were there only girls, in those films?
No!
There were boys as well.
How would I know, he'd be
more interested in looking at boys?
Don't blame me for Aman's behaviour.
Think of the past.
Who introduced me to such movies?
You did!
What about those magazines with
dirty pictures, that you'd keep hidden?
Debo-Nair?
What about those?
Not Debo-Nair, it's Debonair!
At least pronounce it properly.
Don't change the topic.
It's all your fault.
That's all.
You dog, I used to get those
magazines for Shashikant Uncle.
But all of us would enjoy them,
wouldn't we?
It's Uncle's mistake!
Have you lost your mind?
Leave him.
At least pull up your zips,
before you fight, both of you.
Let's go.
You are right.
This taunt of yours...
has really hurt me.
So you are saying,
it is Uncle's mistake.
Let me promise you one thing.
From now on, no uncle in
the family will make such a mistake.
Let's go, Champa.
Wash your hands before touching me.
Go on.
Sunaina, this stinks of revolt.
The stink... is coming from the pee.
Let's go.
Aman is alone with Kusum.
Last night when I found
out that you are gay...
I was thrilled.
But why?
You're the first one
to be thrilled about this.
May I ask, why?
Actually,
I'm in love with someone else.
What?
You're in love with someone else
and that's why you want to marry me?
Why?
I mean, who is this person?
Rakesh.
Sounds unique.
Doesn't it?
He is a simple guy.
He steals cars in Meerut.
In fact,
he's also accused of a murder.
But love is blind, you know.
But he has sworn on his
mother that he didn't do it.
What? Love?
The murder.
He really loves me.
It's my parents who don't like him.
Parents can be crazy, right?
He's such a simple guy
and they still don't like him!
Are you making fun of me?
Did you get Kartik to
sign an application form,
before you fell in love with him?
My parents' problem is that
Rakesh belongs to a different caste.
Sorry.
You don't need to feel guilty.
You have enough problems of your own.
I have an offer.
You are gay.
Alright?
Marry me.
We'll settle down in Delhi.
Rakesh is planning to expand
his business in Delhi, as well.
So, I'll get married to you,
but I'll live with him.
And you can go ahead
and live with Kartik.
Have you lost it?
Why don't you elope with him?
Why are you involving me?
If I elope, I'll miss
out on getting the jewellery.
Just think over it, for a few minutes.
You will have full
freedom after marriage.
How many people are as lucky?
Tell me.
Oh no, your parents
are coming this way.
Tell me if you agree or not.
Yes or no?
Yes or no!
No!
That means yes.
If a girl's refusal is
assumed to be her consent,
the same applies to you as well.
Thank you!
Get away!
Why don't you eat something, Aman?
Don't irritate me.
Romeo was a city boy
While Juliet was a village belle
There's no way the two of them
Could be together, the society decreed
Romeo was a city boy
While Juliet was a village belle
There's no way the two of them
Could be together, the society decreed
They were so much in love
That she ran away from home
There was chaos everywhere
And their love set the village ablaze
Bringing their morality
to a nought, my dear
Congratulations.
We have a boy.
Normal delivery.
What's this new drama, Mummy?
You're a newborn.
You can't talk just yet.
You can just cry.
Look at my face.
I'm doing just that.
Be quiet, or your father
will threaten us with suicide again.
Have you thought of a
new name for your newborn son?
Chandravadhan.
Chandravadhan Tripathi.
Henceforth, Aman will be
known as Chandravadhan Tripathi.
Aman, our first born, has left us.
Just wait a little longer, mister.
The rituals aren't over yet.
They will be, soon.
We have done our job,
fulfilled our responsibility.
What was I saying?
Aman has left us.
We don't know where he is.
In fact, we don't even want to know.
He is dead for us.
We have conducted his last rites.
And done away with his bad habits...
The fact is, Chandravadhan Tripathi
is all set to start his life anew.
Please give him your blessings.
Nonsense!
He should have done this
for our daughter as well.
Shut up.
Who could it be?
- During a curfew?
- I don't know.
- Let me see.
- No, Champa.
It could be those
black cauliflowers again.
But they fall from above, Uncle.
You haven't created ones
that walk through the door, yet.
Goggle is back!
Not here.
Let's go there.
Goggle!
Let's go.
No one even bothered
to come looking for me.
Goggle is...
Brother...
What happened to Aman?
Don't worry, Goggle.
Everything is fine.
See, that's him, standing right there.
I've been trying to convince
your parents for the last two days.
That you are fine.
They need not worry.
We have raised you well.
I can't tell you how happy I am,
to see you.
There were minor problems,
but everything will be okay now.
Our family will come
together and prepare for
Chandravadhan and Kusum's wedding.
Hey, what are you racing towards?
The finish line?
Aman.
In the past.
He has been reborn.
Sorry Uncle, I have no
idea what you guys are up to.
Don't feel bad,
but the cause of your problems...
is up there.
Who is playing the music?
Oh shit.
Chaman!
Are you coming or not, Chaman?
Who is it?
Who is up there?
Who is playing the music?
Oh God!
Chaman, catch that pigeon.
I am sure Karthik
must be behind all this.
I won't.
Chaman, catch that pigeon!
I won't do your bidding anymore.
You're always ordering me around.
From now on, everyone will
solve their problems, by themselves.
Is this how you talk
to your elder brother, Chaman?
Enough, Bhabhi.
I refuse to play the sidekick anymore.
I'll get my degree in
law and play the lead role.
Did you see...
Yes, got it!
I told you, I'll catch you.
You should look over there.
Friends!
Shankar Tripathi is ill.
Very ill.
That man who is featured
in the 'smoking kills' ad...
Mukesh!
He's way more sick than that man is.
It was only Mukesh's
lungs that are affected.
But Shankar Tripathi's lungs,
liver, heart and brain...
...has been taken over
by a dangerous disease.
This disease is called...
Homophobia!
Sounds like a Dolby kind of disease.
Yes.
And this disease has no cure.
What nonsense is this?
I had told you to make
sure he gets on that train.
Where are you all going?
Don't worry, ladies and gentlemen.
This disease is not contagious.
This disease only affects the mind.
Stop him.
Unfortunately this
is not a killer disease...
But...
What are you doing? Let him go.
the diseased man becomes a killer.
There will be films on him.
His story will be oft repeated.
Shankar Tripathi will
be featured on the news.
And one day, Shankar Deenanath
Tripathi will turn into a zombie.
Zombie!
He'll be a zombie.
He'll be... a zombie.
Now that you're back,
I'll deal with you.
Stay right here.
Don't leave.
I'll be back in two minutes.
In two minutes.
He's fooling around, Papa.
I'll deal with him.
No, son, no one will say a word.
He has brought this disease here.
And he will take it back with him.
Papa, I...
- Listen...
- No...
Mummy, why don't you
say something to him?
You always have something to say.
What can I say?
After what you've done,
is there anything left for me to say?
What is he doing wrong?
You are the one who left
home and changed yourself.
But we're still the same.
Please stop this drama, Aunty.
I hope he doesn't own a gun.
If he does, I have a few last
wishes that you could fulfil for me.
I really need to pee, man.
What are you doing?
I was handling everything.
Don't worry, I'll deal with it.
I'm a strong guy.
Uncle, take him away. He's a softie.
Please stop all this.
Kartik, stop this drama right now.
It's not just you,
everyone has to deal
with this kind of crap, bro.
You should leave.
Will you be able to
watch me getting beaten up?
Yes.
I will stand right here.
Today you'll find out, a scientist
can hit as hard as a blacksmith can.
Because that's the way fathers are.
Paying for that single sperm, huh?
I told you.
I'll have to pay for it, all my life.
Now that you are here,
stand your ground.
Don't fall to your knees.
Babe, this guy is crazy about you
He doesn't know if
he's going right or left
He is willing to brave all odds
For the sake of love
I devote my life to you
I'm yours, come what may
My love is one of a kind
Don't you see?
What do you do, my love
When you're away from me?
I sit all alone
Hiding my tears
Every breath I take
Belongs to you
My life will have no meaning
If you lose trust in me
This world envies what we have
And tries to break us apart
I have loved you
Despite what the world had to say
What do you do, my love
When you're away from me?
I sit all alone
Hiding my tears
My sexuality is my sexuality.
None of your sexuality.
He's faking it.
He's still breathing.
You aren't as strong as...
Father used to be.
If there wasn't a curfew, you
could've taken him to the hospital.
I wouldn't have said no.
If there is a police case,
then always remember, I am there.
Yeah, good way to
catch your first client.
Let's go, Champa.
Home?
Is this really our home anymore?
Only a part of it is.
I have to go, Didi is calling me.
Coming!
What did you say, Champa?
- What did she say?
- Got it.
See this article, Uncle.
Sex is actually your gender -
male, female...
Your physical body.
Sexuality is what
you feel from within.
Simple.
That can be different from gender.
How can it differ?
I feel the same way, without
and within, when I feel up your aunt.
If one is physically male,
how can he be a female from within?
I found another article on this.
It is explained in detail,
listen carefully.
Gender is not merely male or female.
Your sexuality can lie
anywhere on this spectrum.
Like, if a woman...
You broke it, Uncle.
No one will utter the word
'sex' in this house anymore.
What word won't you use?
Sex.
Sorry, Uncle.
I won't.
Where is Aman?
Won't he eat dinner?
He has locked himself in his room.
He hasn't come out
since that incident.
I hope he hasn't committed suicide.
Shut up.
I'll go take a look.
I'll come with you, Mummy.
This boy!
Have you lost your mind?
That's what these
youngsters do nowadays.
It has become a trend.
Don't blame me.
This is another one who tried
to kill herself on the rail tracks.
Don't give me that look.
I know what you were
doing on that bridge.
Yes, you know everything.
But you don't know
why I had gone there.
Why do youngsters commit suicide?
Before marriage or after it?
The father tried to kill himself.
Now the son is trying to kill himself.
Maybe I should kill myself
as well and get it over with.
Aman!
Please open the door!
Don't kill yourself
over something so petty.
I had to deal with four rejections.
I didn't run to the
nearest railway tracks.
And you look at you,
taking off on that horse.
Girls, in our time,
were more determined.
We would make sure
that we grab a husband.
Grab?
You mean, have a husband.
You mind your own business.
Children need to
be motivated nowadays.
We didn't need this kind of motivation
although we had problems of our own.
But you had somebody to talk to.
Who do I have?
You had somebody to
share your problems with.
Bade Gulam Ali, the singer.
I loved listening to his sad songs.
Aman, open the door!
Mummy, what will I
do if he kills himself?
Be quiet. Be positive.
- Aman!
- He's my last hope.
Son!
This damn bangle is also stuck.
Try using soap, it'll come off.
Aman!
No matter how hopeless it seems,
one day you will find
someone who loves you.
Chaman will find someone fro you.
I won't let him die before he does.
Let me live in peace until then.
I don't want to get married.
Never ever!
I'll throw you out of the
house if you talk like this.
I dare you to.
This is my home.
Will you hit me with a stick,
- just like you guys hit him?
- Hey!
I have a share in this house.
Forgotten?
Bravo, Chaman!
If you wanted your
share of the property,
you should have spoken to me directly.
Why are you making
her speak on your behalf?
No, Brother.
Never.
What nonsense is this?
She is right.
Bravo.
Champa, nothing could
divide the Tripathis,
and nothing will.
Anyway, there wasn't much to divide.
But we should divide everything now.
Else, the children and their children
will end up fighting with each other.
Your daughter plans to have
children before marriage, does she?
She's 27. I still have hope.
Thanks to your son, you don't.
He has brought home
a son-in-law for you.
How dare you!
Get him to have children first, then
you can stake a claim to the property.
- You can call him a man then!
- Be quiet.
- Mummy, please.
Aman!
- Didi!
- Bhabhi!
Sunaina!
What happened, Bhabhi?
Nothing happened.
See what Guddu has written.
See this.
I promise to marry Kusum,
but Kartik should not be harmed.
Why are you crying then?
Why did you scream?
I screamed because I was happy.
Silly woman.
This...
Is it written in his blood?
No, it's nail polish.
My son...
Where did he go?
Champa, wait and watch, Aman will
get married and have children as well.
We would love that.
Unfortunately, our daughter...
Congratulations, Bhabhi.
Kusum, you too...
Let's forget what just happened.
Why drag children into this?
Things are finally working out well.
Mummy, play louder.
It's your daughter's
wedding after all.
Keep quiet.
Who holds a wedding during a curfew?
Shankar Tripathi does.
Had you ever imagined
that your daughter would be...
...escorted by the police
on her wedding day?
Have you seen this necklace?
It's real gold.
There's more jewellery here.
Show me.
It's mine.
Goggle, why don't
you help me play this?
By the way Aunty,
my name is Rajni, not Goggle.
You go ahead and
play the drum yourself.
You call this a horse?
She will grow up, soon.
In a matter of minutes?
Like in the movies?
Don't shout, Uncle.
It's her first time.
She's a virgin.
I'm not shouting,
I'm merely requesting you.
We can't step out of
the house during the curfew.
We'll get her to walk around
the courtyard a few times,
so that it feels like a real wedding.
And...
- Keshav.
- Coming, Uncle.
Here.
Put this on.
We don't have too many guests.
Feel free to join in the dance.
It's my humble request.
Chaman, what are you waiting for?
Switch the lights on.
Has Article 377 been abolished?
Wait. What the hell is all this?
You're getting married?
To Kusum.
Who is this Kusum?
A girl, Kartik.
Are you okay?
Are you feeling okay?
Haven't you learnt your lesson?
Don't take stress. Take a deep breath.
I don't want to.
We'll talk to her... Suman.
Her name is Kusum, not Suman.
And this was her idea.
Her idea?
She's in love with someone else.
Her parents didn't agree to the match.
Ours would be a fake marriage.
Why the hell do you want
to play house with her then?
Six months down the line,
you'll be asked to have a kid.
One down,
you'll be asked to have another one.
Can you do it?
Will you be able to do it
with your 'legally married wife'?
What else can I do?
I'll have to do it.
I'll have to figure out a
way to deal with this crazy bunch.
OMG!
Way to go.
What a brilliant idea, you dumbass!
First, Sunita and you
will fool your parents.
Her name is Kusum.
Simran and her boyfriend
will then fool her parents.
Her name is Kusum!
Then your parents will
try and fool the society.
Then we will fool them.
At the age of 40, you will realise
that you are the one who has been fooled.
Go. Get married to Sangeeta.
I told you, her name is Kusum!
Aman!
The horse is ready.
So is the bride.
Her name is Kusum!
Please leave.
No chance in hell, Aman Tripathi.
This isn't a game, bro.
Stop playing with my heart.
What do you think, you're in a film,
and the frame will freeze
at the end of your nuptials?
The end. Happy ending.
No way!
You will get roasted
right from your wedding night.
Will you be able to perform,
life long?
Can you play the role
of a dutiful husband?
When she goes gallivanting
with her boyfriend...
will you be able
stay calm when she asks,
'how am I looking baby?'
Can you handle that?
Kartik, I tried my best
to make them understand.
You know I did.
You think you did!
Don't get fooled.
They are your parents.
I'm sure they knew all
along that you're different.
And your father,
the villain of the piece...
he who had celebrated your birth.
He knows that his son likes men.
They are your parents.
They know everything about you...
Right from the beginning.
Your likes,
dislikes, every f*&king thing.
They are unable to accept this,
thinking of
what people would say.
What would society say?
And Shankar Tripathi has
seen this fear in you as well.
You are scared of coming out.
What do I do? Tell me.
What should I do?
Don't get carried away.
He has been fighting this ever
since he saw us, inside the train.
He is ready for a fight.
Unfortunately,
there is no one to take him on.
I have been at the receiving end
of this kind of frustration. Twice.
Are you leaving?
Not so soon.
I'll see you getting married,
before I leave.
Remember one thing,
it's not often that you
get a chance to be a hero.
Now you decide, who you want to be -
the hero or a bystander,
in this story.
Put some more lights up here.
Sunaina?
You're here.
Aren't you ready?
- Listen.
- Yes?
There was something else
written on that piece of paper.
What was written on it?
One minute, I'll show it to you.
On the back it is written -
The legality of Article 377...
Let me close the door.
The Supreme Court will decide
the legality of Article 377, tomorrow.
It means, tomorrow it will be decided
whether what Aman and Kartik
are doing, is legal or not.
What do you want me to do?
Pack a bag and leave from here.
I'll ask Chaman to
drop you to the station.
This matter being debated in
the Supreme Court affects us as well.
Tomorrow, if the Court decides
that homosexuality is not a crime...
Then what?
You'll be thrown in jail
for torturing Aman and Kartik.
You can go ahead and ask them
these questions when you're in jail.
Even if our son doesn't, that boy...
Kartik will definitely
file a case against you.
Why did you beat him so mercilessly?
I won't be the only one going to jail.
All of you are involved in this.
The entire family will go to jail.
I won't.
I am the mother.
I'll say I was busy in the kitchen
when you guys were doing all this.
And you'll send me to jail?
So now, the Supreme Court will
decide for us, what's right and wrong?
Yes, that's what they do.
Do you have any higher
authority than them?
And we don't understand anything?
No, you don't.
I'll say that I've
learnt the truth just now.
I had to give up my studies
after I got married to this man.
I am an uneducated woman after all.
So much to do at home.
Sunaina, don't pretend
to be a helpless woman.
I wasn't alone in all this.
Who beat up that boy?
Why didn't you stop me?
Who got the stick?
You...
It has been 25 years, Mr. Tripathi.
It's high time you got your aim right.
Sunaina,
why get into this argument today?
Throwing me to the wolves so
that you can become the ideal mother?
Of course, I am the ideal mother.
Mothers are run by emotions.
And fathers run on batteries, right?
Can't say about the others...
All I can say is,
for the past 25 years,
you've been living
with me half-heartedly.
You'd given away half of your
heart to Rani, before we got married.
Brother!
Did you have sex with her?
First you tell me.
What all have you done with Kumar?
What hurt you more?
Giving up your studies
or giving up Kumar?
You must really miss her!
You're always sitting in the bathroom!
Brother!
Aman is ready.
We are coming!
Your brother is upset, again!
You could also get upset sometimes.
Disgusting.
Same to you, Sunaina.
Same to you.
I have seen your Facebook account.
There are multiple searches for Kumar.
Why?
Why don't you answer?
Cat got your tongue?
Tell me!
I only searched for him online,
but you... have an entire
album full of Rani's photos.
We are ruining his life.
We are forcing him to live a life
that he doesn't want to. Just like us.
We are bad people.
No, we are not.
Would good people
do something like this?
We aren't good either.
We are just people.
I am not feeling bad about it.
What can I do?
Sunaina, let him get married.
Everything will be fine.
I swear.
He has made a promise.
Where's that sheet of paper?
We'll show that paper to
the police and nothing will happen.
He is our son.
Okay?
Our guests have arrived.
Let's not mess things up now.
Okay?
Why are you wasting time?
Get lost.
This is your science.
And these worms your nature
Let me see if there is any science
that can change your son's nature.
Congratulations on the wedding.
In the previous episode
you saw how Kusum
agreed to marry Shankar Tripathi's
gay son and fooled the entire family.
The desperate and unsuspecting mother
handed over all her jewellery to Kusum.
And Kusum ran away with all
the jewellery, before the wedding.
To guard their son's secret no one
will lodge a complaint against Kusum.
Kusum is a free bird now.
She has fought for her
love and earned her freedom.
Will the Tripathi family
be able to overcome this?
Will Aman be able
to fight his own battle?
Who cares!
Rakesh's lover, Kusum.
What!
She ran away.
What the hell!
Should I get the bride, Panditji?
She has all my jewellery.
Should I get her?
Goggle, go and get her.
Why?
Go.
Children these days...
Are you ready? Bhabhi!
Kusum?
The Panditji wants you there.
I don't really care
about this wedding.
My brother's life
is getting ruined anyway.
Hello!
Do you want to get married or not?
Why are you wearing this shawl?
I'm shivering.
It's too cold, ya.
Goggle! Hurry up.
I'll be right there.
Be patient. It takes time
for a bride to get ready and come.
Haven't yet found someone for me,
in 27 years...
you're in a big hurry
to get your son married!
Do you want me to carry you down?
Let's go!
Woman, what are you waiting for?
'Here comes the bride'?
There's a curfew in the city.
Hurry up.
How have you worn the saree?
It's me Kartik, Goggle.
I hope they don't recognise me.
Where's Kusum?
She has run away.
Run away?
Just in case something goes wrong,
please save my ass.
If something goes wrong.
If?
If you manage to stay alive
till the ceremony gets over,
I'll give you 100 bucks.
Remember, I'd saved your life earlier.
Yes, but that was
from the Indian railways.
We're dealing with
the Tripathi clan here.
No one can save you now.
Please call the bride.
Where were you?
What do you mean?
I was getting her ready.
It takes time.
Where are you going?
Why are you sulking?
At least someone is happy here.
Our daughter will also be happy,
one day.
Has she always been this tall?
She's wearing heels. Be quiet.
Are you okay, my dear?
Do you want something?
Are you feeling cold?
Her hands are so hairy.
Didn't she get her arms waxed?
She's a modern girl.
She wants Aman to accept
her the way she is.
But she did go to the salon,
didn't she?
She took money from me.
Relax, Aunty.
Aren't you going a little slow,Panditji?
Yes.
Get ready for the vows.
Come on, stand up.
One minute.
Mummy!
Are you drunk?
One minute.
Why are you following her?
She's not going anywhere.
Where are you going?
Just a minute.
Pause.
I want to lift the veil.
Whose?
The bride's.
What are you saying?
The bride does not show her
face before the wedding is over.
And certainly not
to her father-in-law.
But I want to.
Are you mad?
Why are you insisting?
Why do you want to see her face?
Because I want to.
That's it.
If you must, here, lift my veil.
Why do you want to lift her veil?
Lift mine!
No, I want to lift hers.
This is too much, Mr. Tripathi.
- Can't you see how scared she is?
- I'm scared.
What a dirty mind!
Absolutely correct.
I have a dirty mind.
But, at least I have a mind.
Which none of you seem to have.
One minute.
Calm down.
Be patient.
Give me a moment.
What are you doing?
Chaman, stop her.
No I won't, Brother.
Do it yourself.
You can have half the property.
Just stop her.
Go!
Why is Papa doing this, Mummy?
Forget him,
why does Kusum keep running away?
It's not Kusum. It's Kartik.
Catch him.
What's wrong with you, Kartik?
Why are you after him?
Kusum is the one who ran away.
Look at this.
She has run away with
all your jewellery, Aunty.
All my jewellery?
Fake jewellery is the best,
I told you so.
Our daughter-in-law has run away and
you're more worried about your jewellery?
It's my wedding jewellery.
The jewellery maybe gone,
but you are safe.
Stay away!
Catch him.
What the hell are you doing, Kartik?
Chaman, catch him!
Why are you going there?
Where are my shoes, Keshav?
Kartik! Uncle, what...!
I got him, Brother!
Caught behind!
Take if off.
Take off the sari.
Why?
Won't you take it off for me?
- Stop, Papa. This is enough.
- Why are you doing this?
Why are you doing this?
The people you are trying to impress,
they're laughing at you.
They aren't laughing at Kartik or me.
They are laughing at your antics.
I don't feel sorry for you.
Do you know why?
Because I had never
expected you to understand.
I have been quiet all my life.
Because I couldn't see you like this.
What are you saying, Aman?
He's your father.
Not everyone is lucky to have one.
Ask me about it.
I had told you, they won't understand.
Of course, they won't.
They have no idea.
They are familiar with Romeo
Juliet and other love stories.
But our kind of love... is
something unfamiliar to them.
They won't understand.
And what they don't understand,
they try to stifle.
Don't worry.
It's our battle and
we will fight it ourselves.
Let's go, Aman.
Just a minute.
Tell me something.
Does the fact that I love this man,
change our relationship in any way?
Why the hell do sons have
to save the day every time?
Fathers can save the day as well!
And Mummy,
you may have lost your jewellery now.
But you'd lost your
son much before this.
Now that you've lost it all,
why stop at this.
Let's go all the way.
Let's go, Kartik.
Panditji, let's start the nuptials.
But you haven't proposed to me yet.
Mummy, get ready for this.
This kind of a wedding will
be more common in the coming years.
Panditji, let's start.
It's time to set an example.
No.
I cannot be a part of this.
Fine, Panditji,
why don't you sing a song instead?
It's just a formality.
The entire family is already here.
They will get busy with
their lives from tomorrow.
And who knows what the Court
is going to decide tomorrow.
See, Panditji...
according to the scriptures, marriage
is a union of two souls, right?
Do souls have a gender?
No.
Then start singing, bro!
This friendship is something
we will never give up.
I am willing to give up my life,
but I am never willing to give you up.
This friendship...
No one will move.
We have come to arrest these two.
According to Article 377,
being gay is a crime.
A crime that is being
committed openly here.
What are you saying?
How can you just arrest these boys?
We will have to arrest them.
Please don't interfere.
Arrest these lover boys.
One minute.
Do something.
Stop them!
Let's go.
Alright, Inspector,
you can take them away.
He's the father.
There isn't much he is capable of,
except sulk.
And he's the son, he expects
us to change our beliefs overnight.
Take them away.
Let's end this matter.
The family was falling apart anyway.
Shankar Tripathi isn't capable
of putting up a fight anymore.
Come on, let's go.
Wait.
Just a minute, Inspector.
This is our house.
Our family.
And this is our
personal family matter.
We will deal with it.
According to law,
being gay is a crime, Uncle.
Excuse me.
Move aside, Champa.
- Go from that side!
- Okay.
Don't try to teach me the law,
Inspector.
My name is Chaman Tripathi.
I am their family lawyer.
And a part of their family as well.
So... according to law,
being gay is a crime.
- Okay?
- Okay.
But how can you assume
that these two are gay?
I see.
Get her.
This girl has told us everything.
We caught her at the bus
stop with all the jewellery.
The jewellery that she has stolen.
Who is she to decide
whether they are gay or not?
Tell me, have you caught
them doing anything
that made you believe
that they are gay?
Go on. Tell me.
I am their lawyer.
No, you haven't.
Then how will you prove this in court?
How?
Let me present my next argument.
Champa!
Give me your blessings, Brother.
If two consenting adult men hold hands
or do anything in the confines
of their bedroom... Bhabhi...
Then you, me or anyone for that
matter, should not have any objection.
Well done.
Well done, Mr. Lawyer.
Right?
Inspector, whatever they are doing,
it's their choice.
When we don't have the right to question
their choice, who are you to interfere?
- Like I said, the law...
- Which can change tomorrow.
You may come tomorrow, after the
Supreme Court has passed its judgement.
Until then... Keshav!
They are free to go.
- Okay, Uncle.
- Please.
Let's go.
If you don't mind, Mr. Tripathi,
we will stay right here.
Until the ruling is passed,
we have to follow the law.
The accused may run away.
What's wrong is wrong.
Yes, what's wrong is wrong.
Of course. Let me invite you to stay.
We have a lot of food
and not too many guests.
We have some tasty
black cauliflower snacks.
They are very nutritious.
You must try some.
We are on duty. It's not allowed.
It's black cauliflower I'm offering,
not black money.
Come with me.
They say, love shouldn't cross limits
They, who have never been in love
This heart is a simpleton
Unable to fathom the ways of the world
They may think they know us
But they don't
We may get finished
But our passion will remain
The embers of our love will
Burn on
Our misty eyes Will forever
Hope for happiness
We may get finished
But our passion will remain
The embers of our love will
Burn on
Our misty eyes
Will forever
Hope for happiness
Love will not be stifled
And driven away by fear
The embers of hope will remain
And will grow from the pain
We will grow stronger
With every blow
'Breaking News!'
'The Supreme Court has passed
a landmark judgement on homosexuality.'
'In their judgement,
Supreme Court has stated that'
'same-gender, private relationships
between two consenting adults,'
'will not be considered a crime.'
We may get finished
But our passion will remain
The embers of our love will
Burn on
Our misty eyes
Will forever
Hope for happiness
No matter how harsh the axe
The root will find a way to live
One love, one war
Both are at fault
Will have to find a way together
It's hard enough to control my heart
I don't care about what people say
Let me drop you off at the station.
Come Kartik, Papa will drop us.
I won't sit on the bike.
But why?
I want to drive it.
- I won't let you.
- I want to drive it.
Drive it.
Let him ride.
I'll drive.
We may get finished
But our passion will remain
The embers of our love will
Burn on
Our misty eyes
Will forever
Hope for happiness
Okay, Papa.
Don't call me Papa.
Papaji?
Papa is fine.
I don't know...
if I will ever understand this thing.
But don't let me stop you
from living your life to the fullest.
Go ahead and live your life, son.
Go.
Hurry up or you'll miss the train.
We are running for love.
Just like Laila would have,
for Juliet.
Majnu would have, for Romeo.
Simran would have, for Anjali.
Veeru would have perhaps, for Jai.
Weddings happen at a fixed time,
but there is no fixed
time to fall in love.
Love has no fixed colour or gender.
We have to remove the restrictions
we impose on our hearts...
to be with the one we love.
Until then
we'll keep running
for our love.